Guide to the Fales Manuscript Collection circa 1700-2000 MSS.001
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Letter sized boxes, 47643
  - Greene, Graham (1904- ), undated; 50386 (Box 76, Folder 7b)
  - Greenland, George A.: [gift of Professor Joel Egerer, August 17, 1964], undated; 50385 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Greenough, Sara Dana (Loring) (1827-1885), undated; 50384 (Box 76, Folder 9a)
  - Greenwood, Frederick (1830-1909), undated; 50383 (Box 76, Folder 9b)
  - [Greenwood, Grace: see Lippincott, Sara Jane (Clarke), Box 110], 1690-2000; 50382 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_2b8a2de2d756ed475ea8f421808a73d4)
  - Greet, Clare, undated; 50381 (Box 76, Folder 9c)
  - Gregory XVI, Pope (1765-1846): Signed Engraving, undated; 50380 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Gregory, Alyse, undated; 50379 (Box 76, Folder 9e)
  - Greenwich Village: Ephemera, undated; 50378 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Gregory, Isabella Augusta (Persse), Lady: 7 Letters; 1 Mat., undated; 50377 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Greig, Maysie (1902- ), undated; 50376 (Box 76, Folder 12a)
  - Grey, Edward Grey, 1st Viscount of Felloden (1862-1933), undated; 50375 (Box 76, Folder 12b)
  - Grey, Zane (1872-1939), undated; 50374 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): List of Holdings [see also Legal Size & Galleys], undated; 50373 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): Correspondence [see also Legal Size], undated; 50372 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Carotid Cornucopius [see also Legal Size & Galleys], undated; 50371 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Carotid Cornucopius, undated; 50370 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Carotid Cornucopius [early version of Section 1, also Section 1 & 2, Sections 1-4], undated; 50369 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Carotid Cornucopius [Sections 1-4], undated; 50368 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. The Case of Alice Carruthers, undated; 50367 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Hamilton Rotary Club Talk, undated; 50366 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. In the Gaelic Islands, undated; 50365 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Lewis Grassic Gibbon, undated; 50364 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. M.M.C. Notes [2 notebooks], undated; 50363 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): Printed Materials. The Present Condition of Scottish Arts and Affairs [Gift of Bart Auerbach, Jan. 1964], undated; 50362 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Scottish Arts and Affairs [Scoto-Gaelic Literature], undated; 50361 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Red Scotland, undated; 50360 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Scotland and the United States of Europe, undated; 50359 (Box 77, Folder 15a)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Unique Typescript of Selected Poems of Hugh McDiarmid, undated; 50358 (Box 77, Folder 15b)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): MS. Introduction: Dunbar, William. Selected Poems, undated; 50357 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): [Grieve, Christopher M.] Trevlyn, Valda: Hugh MacDiarmid and the Scottish Landscape, undated; 50356 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Grieve, Christopher M. (Hugh MacDiarmid): [Pictorial] Original Drawing by Stephen Spurrier, undated; 50355 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Grigson, Baseley H.: 14 A.L.s., undated; 50354 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Griswold, Rufus W., undated; 50353 (Box 78, Folder 2a)
  - Grote, George (1794-1871), undated; 50352 (Box 78, Folder 2b)
  - Grote, Harriet (1792-1878), undated; 50351 (Box 78, Folder 2c)
  - Grove, Sir George (1820-1900), undated; 50350 (Box 78, Folder 3a)
  - Guerland, Albert Leon (1880-), undated; 50349 (Box 78, Folder 3b)
  - Guillot, Adolphe, undated; 50348 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Guiney, Louise Imogen (1861-1920), undated; 50347 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Guiterman, Arthur: MS. Poems [published, in alphabetical order], undated; 50346 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Guiterman, Arthur: MS. Poems [see also Legal Size for pre-1909], undated; 50345 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Guiterman, Arthur: MS. Poems [published, not in books, A-H], undated; 50344 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Guiterman, Arthur: MS. Poems [published, not in books, I-Z], undated; 50343 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Guiterman, Arthur: MS. Poems [unpublished?, A-O], undated; 50342 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Guiterman, Arthur: MS. Poems [unpublished, P-Z], undated; 50341 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Gull, Cyril Arthur E.R. (1876-1923), undated; 50340 (Box 78, Folder 12a)
  - Gunn, Neil Miller (1891- ), undated; 50339 (Box 78, Folder 12b)
  - Gunter, Archibald Clavering (1847-1907), undated; 50338 (Box 78, Folder 12c)
  - Guthrie, Charles John Guthrie, Lord (1849-1920): MS. R.L.S. at College, undated; 50337 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Guthrie, Thomas Anstey (1856-1934), undated; 50336 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Gwynn, Stephen Lucius (1864-1950), undated; 50335 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Habberton, John (1842-1921), undated; 50334 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Habberton, John (1842-1921): MS. The Hypocrisy of Pull, undated; 50333 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Haggard, Henry Rider, Sir (1856-1925): 1882-1923, 50332 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Haggard, Henry Rider, Sir (1856-1925): Miscellaneous Correspondence [see also Legal Size], undated; 50331 (Box 79, Folder 4a)
  - Haggard, Lilias Rider: 1 A.L.s., MS. [Mat], undated; 50330 (Box 79, Folder 4b)
  - Haggard, Henry Rider, Sir (1856-1925): MS. Beatrice [Galley to Adv., 1894], undated; 50329 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Haight, Gordon S., undated; 50328 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Hale, Edward Everett (1822-1909): 1845-1875, 50327 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Hale, Edward Everett (1822-1909): 1880-1892; undated, 50326 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Hale, Sarah Josepha (Buell) (1788-1879), undated; 50325 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Halegua, Lillian: MS. The Priest plus 2 A.L.s., 1966; 50324 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Halegua, Lillian: MS. [carbon] The Priest, undated; 50323 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Halford, John, undated; 50322 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Haliburton, Thomas Chandler (1796-1865), undated; 50321 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Hall, Anna Maria (1800-1881), undated; 50320 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Hall, Basil (1788-1844), undated; 50319 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Hall, James Norman (1887-1951): 2 A.L.s., undated; 50318 (Box 79, Folder 16a)
  - Hall, Radclyffe (188?-1943): 1 A.L.s., undated; 50317 (Box 79, Folder 16b)
  - Hall, Samuel Carter (1800-1889): 4 A.L.s., undated; 50316 (Box 79, Folder 16c)
  - Hallam, Henry (1777-1859), undated; 50315 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Halleck, Fitz-Greene (1790-1867), undated; 50314 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Halliwell-Phillipps, James Orchard (1820-1889), undated; 50313 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Hamerton, Philip Gilbert (1834-1894), undated; 50312 (Box 79, Folder 20a)
  - Hamilton, Cosmo, undated; 50311 (Box 79, Folder 20b)
  - [Hamilton, Gail: see Dodge, Mary Abigail, Box 46], 1690-2000; 50310 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_979afb467d3694e9112927aebc62ae51)
  - Hamilton, Marie, undated; 50309 (Box 79, Folder 20c)
  - Hamilton, William Rowen, Sir (1805-1865), undated; 50308 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910): Pictorial, The Absentee [1894, 10 pp. proofs], 50307 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910): Pictorial, The Absentee [1894, 11 pp. proofs], 50306 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910): Pictorial, The Absentee [1894, 11 pp. proofs], 50305 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910): Pictorial, Castle Rackrent [1894, 19 pp. proof], 50304 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910): Pictorial, Marmonte's Moral Tales [1895, 36 drawings], 50303 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910): Pictorial, The Good Natured Man [1896, 15 pp. proofs], 50302 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910): Pictorial, She Stoops to Conquer, undated; 50301 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910): Pictorial, She Stoops to Conquer, undated; 50300 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910): Pictorial [removed from] She Stoops to Conquer, undated; 50299 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910), undated; 50298 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910), undated; 50297 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910), undated; 50296 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910), undated; 50295 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Hammond, Christine M. Demain (fl. 1886-1910), undated; 50294 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Hamper, William (1776-1831), undated; 50293 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Hankin, St. John Emile Clavering (1869-1909): 2 Letters, undated; 50292 (Box 81, Folder 2a)
  - Hanley, James (1901- ): 5 Letters [see also Oversize, 2 Letters], undated; 50291 (Box 81, Folder 2b)
  - Hanley, Jennifer: 1 Letter, undated; 50290 (Box 81, Folder 2c)
  - Hanline, Maurice A.: Fragments of Fears and Other Poems and Plays, undated; 50289 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Hapgood, Isabel Florence (1850-1928), undated; 50288 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Harben, William Nathaniel (1858-1919): 1 Letter, 1 Photograph., undated; 50287 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - [Hardy, Thomas: see Boxes 82 & 82.5], 1690-2000; 50286 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_bd38ededa2714999031be2aab268bc9c)
  - Hare, Augustus J. C. (1834-1903): 5 Letters, undated; 50285 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Harland, Henry (1861-1905): 1 Letter to Miss Curtis [May 9th], 1 Letter to Edmund Gosse [June 21, 1903], 1 Letter to Mrs. Leverson [October 23, 1895], 1895-1903; 50284 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - [Harland, Marion: see Terhune, Mary Virginia Hawes, Boxes 177 & Legal Size 17], 1690-2000; 50283 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_396f7adaa19e43b83417a4e606fbbf7c)
  - Harlow, Alvin F.: 1 Mat. The Devil's Hopper [unpublished], undated; 50282 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Harraden, Beatrice (1864-1936): undated [2 of 2], 50281 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Harraden, Beatrice (1864-1936): 1894-1919 [1 of 2], 50280 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Harris, Corra, undated; 50279 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - [Harris, Frank: see Boxes 83-86.2], 1690-2000; 50278 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_52dc794aee497bb9c787991f00fe0ea2)
  - Hardy, Florence Emily (1881-1937); Hardy, Emma Lavinia Gifford (1840-1912): undated; 1894; 1924, 50277 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Hardy, Henry: Life of Thomas Hardy, 1916; 50276 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Addenda, undated; 50275 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): MATs., undated; 50274 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Correspondence [1877-1899], 50273 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Correspondence [1900-1909], 50272 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Correspondence [1910-1921], 50271 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): MS. Among the Roman Gravemounds [see also Oversize], undated; 50270 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Tess of the T'Ubervilles [Drama; Box Office, 1897], 50269 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Tess of the T'Ubervilles [Drama; Box Office, January -April 1898], 50268 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Tess of the T'Ubervilles [Drama; Box Office, October -December 1898], 50267 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Tess of the T'Ubervilles [Drama; Treasurer's Statement, 1898], 50266 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Tess of the T'Ubervilles [Drama; Box Office, January 1899- ], 50265 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): ca. 1920s; undated, 50264 (Box 82.5, Folder 1)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Pictorial, undated; 50263 (Box 82.5, Folder 2)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Greeting Cards, undated; 50262 (Box 82.5, Folder 3)
  - Hardy, Thomas (1840-1928): Jezreel the Master [note to Clement Short enclosed]; Two Phantasies, undated; 50261 (Box 82.5, Folder 4)
  - [Hardy, Thomas]: Memorial Service to T.H.; Letters re Memorial Service, undated; 50260 (Box 82.5, Folder 5)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Correspondence, undated; 50259 (Box 83, Folder 1a)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Correspondence to A - Z, undated; 50258 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Correspondence to Pearson, Hesketh [see also Legal Size], undated; 50257 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Correspondence to Ross, Arthur L., undated; 50256 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Correspondence to Shaw, G. B. [see also Legal Size], undated; 50255 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Correspondence to White, Maurice, 1919-1929; 50254 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Correspondence from A - Z, undated; 50253 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Correspondence from Alice, Princess of Monaco [copies], undated; 50252 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Correspondence from Churchill, Winston [copies], undated; 50251 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Printed Matter, undated; 50250 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Butterworth / Landau, Hammel, undated; 50249 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Nellie Harris / A. E. Ross, 1927-1954, 50248 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Nellie Harris, Miscellaneous, undated; 50247 (Box 83.5, Folder 1)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Lyngklip, Pauline and Einar, undated; 50246 (Box 83.5, Folder 2)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L., Letters to A.L.R., undated; 50245 (Box 83.5, Folder 3)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L. / Mrs. Patrick Campbell, undated; 50244 (Box 83.5, Folder 4)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L., Letters to A.L.R.; Henry Miller, undated; 50243 (Box 83.5, Folder 5)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L. / Hesketh Pearson Correspondence, undated; 50242 (Box 83.5, Folder 6)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L. [Business], undated; 50241 (Box 83.5, Folder 7)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L. [Business]; Montes the Matador [film], undated; 50240 (Box 83.5, Folder 8)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L. [Business]; My Life and Loves [see also Legal Size], undated; 50239 (Box 83.5, Folder 9)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L. [Business]; Oscar Wilde Lawsuit [Stokes v. Harris], undated; 50238 (Box 83.5, Folder 10)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L. [Business]; Reminiscences of a Cowboy [motion picture], undated; 50237 (Box 83.5, Folder 11)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Ross, A. L. [Business]; Shaw, Collected Letters, undated; 50236 (Box 83.5, Folder 12)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Tarbeaux, Frank; Tarboy, undated; 50235 (Box 83.5, Folder 13)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Petition to the French Court, undated; 50234 (Box 83.5, Folder 14)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Clippings, undated; 50233 (Box 83.5, Folder 15)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Photographs, Negatives, undated; 50232 (Box 83.5, Folder 16)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Miscellaneous Printed Material, undated; 50231 (Box 83.5, Folder 17)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): MS. Bernard Shaw 1-19 [Ross's copy], undated; 50230 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): MS. Bernard Shaw 20- [Ross's copy], undated; 50229 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): MS. Bernard Shaw 20- [Ross's copy], undated; 50228 (Box 84.3, Folder 1)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): MS. Bernard Shaw [112 pp., Early Draft w/ Corrections], undated; 50227 (Box 84.3, Folder 2)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): MS. Bernard Shaw [106 pp., Later Draft w/ Corrections], undated; 50226 (Box 84.3, Folder 3)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): MS. Beyond Good and Evil, undated; 50225 (Box 84.3, Folder 4)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): MS. Collected Letters, undated; 50224 (Box 84.6, Folder 1)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): MS. Collected Letters [gift of editor's widow], undated; 50223 (Box 84.6, Folder 2)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): MS. Contemporary Portraits, Vol. 6 [pt. 1] [1-15], undated; 50222 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): MS. Contemporary Portraits, Vol. 6 [pt. 2], undated; 50221 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): MS. Critical Essays, Chapter 25, Anti-Semitism, undated; 50220 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): MS. Joan La Rome´e, undated; 50219 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): MS. There I Lie Dead, undated; 50218 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): MS. The Veils of Isis, undated; 50217 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Life and Loves [Galleys], undated; 50216 (Box 86.1, Folder My)
  - Harris, Frank (1855-1931): Life and Loves [Galleys], undated; 50215 (Box 86.2, Folder My)
  - Harris, Joel Chandler, undated; 50214 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - [Harris, Joel Chandler] Illustrations 1) Herford, Oliver, 2) Kemble, E.W., undated; 50213 (Box 87, Folder 2a)
  - Harris, Miriam Coles [Mrs. Sydney S. Harris] (1834-1925), undated; 50212 (Box 87, Folder 2b)
  - Harrison, Constance Cary (1843-1920) "Mrs. Burton Harrison", undated; 50211 (Box 87, Folder 3a)
  - Harrison, Frederic (1831-1923), undated; 50210 (Box 87, Folder 3b)
  - Harrison, Henry Sydnor (1880-1930), undated; 50209 (Box 87, Folder 3c)
  - Harrison, Mary St. Leger Kingsley (1852-1931), undated; 50208 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Hart, Solomon Alexander (1806-1881), undated; 50207 (Box 87, Folder 3e)
  - Harte, Bret (1836-1902), undated; 50206 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Hartmann, Cyril Hughes (1896- ), undated; 50205 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Hartmann, Sadakichi: Correspondence, undated; 50204 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Hartmann, Sadakichi: Correspondence to Raymond Brossard, undated; 50203 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Hartmann, Sadakichi: Self-Portrait, undated; 50202 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Hartmann, Sadakichi: MS. Drifting Flowers of the Sea, undated; 50201 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Hartmann, Sadakichi: MS. Naked Ghosts, undated; 50200 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Hartmann, Sadakichi: MS. Prose Poems, undated; 50199 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Hartmann, Sadakichi: [Reitz, Josef: Music MS. Sadakichi March], undated; 50198 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Harvey, Alexander (1868-1949), undated; 50197 (Box 87, Folder 13a)
  - Harvey, George, undated; 50196 (Box 87, Folder 13b)
  - Harvey, James Clarence, undated; 50195 (Box 87, Folder 13c)
  - Hassal, Christopher Vernon (1912- ), undated; 50194 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Hatheway, William, undated; 50193 (Box 87, Folder 13e)
  - Hawkins, Anthony Hope: Correspondence [1894-1901], 50192 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Hawkins, Anthony Hope: Correspondence [1902-1914], 50191 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Hawkins, Anthony Hope: Correspondence [1915-1933; undated], 50190 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Hawkins, Anthony Hope: MS. Lucinda [synopsis], undated; 50189 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Hawthorne, Julian (1846-1934) [and Edith Garrigues Hawthorne]: [see also Legal Size], undated; 50188 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Hawthorne, Nathaniel [see also Legal Size for Wonder Book, p. 8], undated; 50187 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - Hay, James, undated; 50186 (Box 88, Folder 1a)
  - Hay, John, undated; 50185 (Box 88, Folder 1b)
  - Hay, Sara Henderson, undated; 50184 (Box 88, Folder 1c)
  - Hayden, Ferdinand Vandeveer (1829-1887), undated; 50183 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Hazlitt, William Carew (1834-1913), undated; 50182 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Healy, Timothy Michael (1855-1931), undated; 50181 (Box 88, Folder 3a)
  - Heaney, Seamus: [Facsimile], undated; 50180 (Box 88, Folder 3b)
  - Hearn, Lafcadio (1850-1904), undated; 50179 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Heath, Charles (1785-1848), undated; 50178 (Box 88, Folder 5a)
  - Heber, R[eginald?], undated; 50177 (Box 88, Folder 5b)
  - Heber, Richard (1773-1833), undated; 50176 (Box 88, Folder 5c)
  - "Heather Bells" [illuminated MS.], undated; 50175 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Hecht, Ben, undated; 50174 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Hector, Annie, undated; 50173 (Box 88, Folder 8a)
  - Heestand, N. D., undated; 50172 (Box 88, Folder 8b)
  - Helle, Benjamin D.P.M., undated; 50171 (Box 88, Folder 8c)
  - Heller, Joseph, undated; 50170 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Helprin, Mark, undated; 50169 (Box 88, Folder 9a)
  - Helps, Arthur, Sir, undated; 50168 (Box 88, Folder 9b)
  - Hellman, Sam, undated; 50167 (Box 88, Folder 10a)
  - Helper, Hinton Rowan (1829-1909), undated; 50166 (Box 88, Folder 10b)
  - Hemans, Felicia: Correspondence 1, undated; 50165 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Hemans, Felicia: Correspondence 2, undated; 50164 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Hemans, Felicia: MS., undated; 50163 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Hemans, Felicia: MS. Commonplace Book, undated; 50162 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Hemingway, Ernest: "Bastard note" fasc., poems, undated; 50161 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Hemingway, Ernest: clippings, undated; 50160 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Hemingway, Ernest: Nobody Ever Dies [in Cosmopolitan Magazine], undated; 50159 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Hemingway, Ernest: Short, Happy Life of Francis Macomber [in Cosmopolitan Magazine] [September 1936], 50158 (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Hemingway, Ernest: Under the Ridge, undated; 50157 (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Henley, William Ernest (1849-1903), 1885-1903; 50156 (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - Henschel, George, undated; 50155 (Box 88, Folder 21a)
  - Henty, George Alfred (1832-1902), undated; 50154 (Box 88, Folder 21b)
  - Heraud, John A., undated; 50153 (Box 88, Folder 22a)
  - Herbert, Alan Patrick, undated; 50152 (Box 88, Folder 22b)
  - Herbert, Auberon Edward William Molyneux (1838-1906), undated; 50151 (Box 88, Folder 23a)
  - Herbert, Elizabeth (A'Court), Lady, undated; 50150 (Box 88, Folder 23b)
  - Herford, Margaret (Regan) (Mrs. Oliver Herford) ( -1935), undated; 50149 (Box 88, Folder 24a)
  - Herford, Oliver (1863-1935), undated; 50148 (Box 88, Folder 24b)
  - Hergesheimer, Joseph (1880-1954), undated; 50147 (Box 88, Folder 25)
  - Heron-Allen, Edward (1861-1943): 17 ALs to Heron-Allen, undated; 50146 (Box 88, Folder 26)
  - Herrick, Robert (1868-1935), undated; 50145 (Box 88, Folder 27a)
  - Herschel, John Frederick Willi, Sir, undated; 50144 (Box 88, Folder 27b)
  - Hersey, John, undated; 50143 (Box 88, Folder 27c)
  - Hervey, Thomas Kibble (1799-1859), undated; 50142 (Box 88, Folder 28a)
  - Herzog, Paul, Mrs., undated; 50141 (Box 88, Folder 28b)
  - Hesketh, Harriet, Lady (1733-1807), undated; 50140 (Box 88, Folder 28c)
  - Hewitt, Mary E., undated; 50139 (Box 88, Folder 28)
  - Hewardine, Matthew B. (illustrations): 23 drawings [Reade, Charles: The Cloister and the Hearth], undated; 50138 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Hewlett, Maurice Henry (1861-1923): 1896-1914 [see also Legal Size for MSS.], 50137 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Hewlett, Maurice Henry (1861-1923): 1915-1922, 50136 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Hewlett, Maurice Henry (1861-1923): 1923; undated, 50135 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Hicks, Granville: to Oscar Cargill, undated; 50134 (Box 89, Folder 5a)
  - Hicky, Daniel Whitehead (1902- ), undated; 50133 (Box 89, Folder 5b)
  - Higgins, F.R., undated; 50132 (Box 89, Folder 5c)
  - Higgins, Dick (1938- ), undated; 50131 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Higginson, Thomas Wentworth (1825-1911), undated; 50130 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Hill, Constance (1844-1929): MS. Story of the Princess des Ursins...; 1905 Preface to 2nd edition, undated; 50129 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Hill, Frederick Trevor (1866-1930), undated; 50128 (Box 89, Folder 9a)
  - Hill, Grace Livingston (1865-1947), undated; 50127 (Box 89, Folder 9b)
  - Hill, Leonard Erskine, Sir (1866- ), undated; 50126 (Box 89, Folder 9c)
  - Hilliard, George Stillman (1808-1879), undated; 50125 (Box 89, Folder 9)